Guide to the Ruth Ann Overbeck papers & Washington Perspectives, Inc. records, 1663-2007 MS2032
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Publications, Circa 1974-1993; MS2032 Series 5; 1.5 Linear feet
  - Publications on historic preservation: Federal Tax Provisions to Encourage Rehabilitation of Historic Buildings: An Assessment of Their Effect, 1979 (Box 7A, Folder 14)
  - Publications on historic preservation: Guide to Resources Used in Historic Preservation Research, undated (Box 7A, Folder 15)
  - Publications on historic preservation: Legacy Resource Management Program, undated (Box 7A, Folder 16)
  - Publications on historic preservation: Rehabilitating Historic Hotels Peabody Hotel, Memphis TN, 1980 (Box 7A, Folder 17)
  - Publications outside D.C.: An Architectural Study of Some Log Structures in the Area of the Yatesville Lake Lawrence County, Kentucky, 1978 (Box 7B, Folder 1)
  - Publications outside D.C.: Historic Documentation and Archaeological Potential of Nine Historic Sites in the Proposed Yatesville Reservoir, Lawrence County, Kentucky, 1987 (Box 7B, Folder 2)
- Research materials, 1663-2007; MS2032 Series 6; 18.5 Linear feet
  This series is the largest of the collection and includes reports, photographs, research notes, and correspondence related to the work of Ms. Overbeck as an historian. The series is divided into two areas including material related to D.C. research and material for topics outside of the D.C. area. Within each area the material is arranged in alphabetical order. Please note that the last three boxes of this series were discovered following the original processing and are not in proper order for materials for topics outside of D.C. The topic of these boxes is Cross Manor in St. Mary's County Maryland.
  - D.C. Houses: 119 2nd St. NE, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Houses: 108 3rd St. NE, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - D.C. Houses: 415 3rd St. NE and 424 4th St. NE (includes photos), undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - D.C. Houses: 616 3rd St. NE (includes photos), undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - D.C. Houses: 800 3rd St. NE, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Houses: 9 4th St. NE, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - D.C. Houses: 10 4th St. NE, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - D.C. Houses: 441 4th St. NE rear, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - D.C. Houses: 410 5th St. NE Carbery School, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Houses: 129 6th St. NE, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - D.C. Houses: 214 7th St. NE, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - D.C. Houses: 211 8th St. NE, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - D.C. Houses: 9th and Massachusetts Ave. NE, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - D.C. Houses: 21 9th St. NE, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - D.C. Houses: 427 10th St. NE, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - D.C. Houses: 435 10th St. NE, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - D.C. Houses: 206 11th St. NE, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - D.C. Houses: 128 12th St. NE (includes photos), undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - D.C. Houses: 401 11 St. NW, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - D.C. Houses: 1236 11th St. NW The Plymouth, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - D.C. Houses: 2437 15th St. NW, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - D.C. Houses: 1575 16th St. NW Stonesdale Condominiums, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - D.C. Houses: 1836 16th St. NW (includes photos), undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - D.C. Houses: 1919 16th St. NW, undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - D.C. Houses: 1319 18th St. NW (includes photos), undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - D.C. Houses: 1739 19th St. NW, undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - D.C. Houses: 1408 21st St. NW, undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - D.C. Houses: 1314 30th St. NW Grafton Tyler House, undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - D.C. Houses: 500 4th St. SE, undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - D.C. Houses: 521 4th St. SE, undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - D.C. Houses: 222 4th St. SE and 506 9th St. SE and 220 4th St. SE (includes photos), undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - D.C. Houses: 115 5th SE, undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - D.C. Houses: 208 5th St. SE, undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - D.C. Houses: 210 5th St. SE, undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - D.C. Houses: 311, 313, 315 6th St. SE, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Houses: 401 6th St. SE, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - D.C. Houses: 423 6th St. SE The Carbery House, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - D.C. Houses: 732,733,734 6th St. SE, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - D.C. Houses: 21 7th St. SE, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Houses: 223 8th St. SE (includes photos), undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - D.C. Houses: 536 8th St. SE (includes photos), undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - D.C. Houses: 539 8th St. SE (includes photos), undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - D.C. Houses: 541-547 8th St. SE, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Houses: 731 8th St. SE and 1317 F St. NW (includes photos), undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - D.C. Houses: 735 8th St. SE, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - D.C. Houses: 226 9th St. SE, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - D.C. Houses: 510 9th St. SE, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - D.C. Houses: 10 St. SE Crestar Bank, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - D.C. Houses: 505 10th St. SE (includes photos), undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - D.C. Houses: 507 10th St. SE, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - D.C. Houses: 130 11th St. SE, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - D.C. Houses: 150 11th St. SE (includes photos), undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - D.C. Houses: 236 11th St. SE, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - D.C. Houses: 520 11th St. SE and 204 9th St. (includes photos), undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - D.C. Houses: 116 12th and 134 12th St. NE (includes photos), undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - D.C. Houses: 136 12th St. SE (includes photos), undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - D.C. Houses: 315 12th St. SE, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - D.C. Houses: 110 13th St. SE, undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - D.C. Houses: 201 13th St. SE or 205 13th St. SE (includes photos), undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Houses: 623 A. St. NE, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - D.C. Houses: 636 A. St. NE, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - D.C. Houses: 317 C St. NE and 324 Maryland Ave. NE and 913 East Capital St. (includes photos), undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - D.C. Houses: 510 C St. NE, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Houses: 518 C St. NE, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - D.C. Houses: 634 C St. NE (includes photos), undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - D.C. Houses: 901 C St. NE, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - D.C. Houses: 1116 and 1118 C St. NE (includes photos), undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Houses: 227 Constitution Ave. NE, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - D.C. Houses: 629 Constitution Ave. NE, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - D.C. Houses: 631 Constitution Ave. NE, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - D.C. Houses: 804 D St. NE, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - D.C. Houses: 224 E St. NE (includes photos), undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - D.C. Houses: 307 E St. NE (includes photos), undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - D.C. Houses: 401 E St. NE and 442 3rd St. and 231 E St. NE, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - D.C. Houses: 612 E St. NE, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - D.C. Houses: 416 East Capital St. NE, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - D.C. Houses: 500 Block East Capital St. NE north side (page 5 missing), undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - D.C. Houses: 642 East Capital St. NE (includes photos), undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - D.C. Houses: 804 East Capital St. NE, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - D.C. Houses: 904 East Capital St. NE (includes photos), undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - D.C. Houses: 1206 East Capital St. NE, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - D.C. Houses: 300 F St. NE, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - D.C. Houses: 203 Maryland Ave. NE (includes photos), undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - D.C. Houses: 300 Maryland Ave. NE, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - D.C. Houses: 615 Maryland Ave. NE, undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - D.C. Houses: 616-622 Maryland Ave. NE Stanton Row work for Barbara Held, undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - D.C. Houses: 226 Massachusetts Ave. NE, undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - D.C. Houses: 311 Massachusetts Ave. NE (includes photos), undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Houses: 632 Massachusetts Ave. NE (includes photos), undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - D.C. Houses: 901 Newton St. NE Brooks Mansion (Bellair) (1510 Jackson St. & O St. Market) (includes photos), undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - D.C. Houses: 118 Tennessee Ave. NE, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - D.C. Houses: 316 and 318 A St. NW, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Houses: 1768 and 1770 Church St. NW (includes photos), undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - D.C. Houses: 900 Block Columbia Rd. NW, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - D.C. Houses: 1321 Corcoran St. NW Square 240 Lot 22, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - D.C. Houses: 2145 Decatur NW (includes photos), undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Houses: 1206 East Capital St. NW, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - D.C. Houses: 501-509 G St. NW, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - D.C. Houses: 604 H St. NW Mary Surratt House, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - D.C. Houses: 233 Morgan St. NW, undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - D.C. Houses: 2115 N St. NW (includes photos), undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - D.C. Houses: 2225 N St. NW, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - D.C. Houses: 2225 N St. NW, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - D.C. Houses: 2225 N St. NW (includes photos), undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - D.C. Houses: 3405 N St. NW, undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - D.C. Houses: 1701 New Hampshire Ave. NW, undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - D.C. Houses: 1751 New Hampshire Ave. NW, undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - D.C. Houses: 2918 Olive St. NW, undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - D.C. Houses: 1513 Q St. NW, undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - D.C. Houses: 1327 R St. NW Phi Beta Sigma Fraternity, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - D.C. Houses: 1515 U St. NW, undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - D.C. Houses: 1715 U St. NW, undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - D.C. Houses: 16 A St. SE (804/787) and House History, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - D.C. Houses: 412 A St. SE, undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - D.C. Houses: 417 A St. SE (27/818), undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Houses: 613 A St. SE, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - D.C. Houses: 608 B St. SE, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - D.C. Houses: 620 C St. SE, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - D.C. Houses: 922 C St. SE, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Houses: 49 D St. SE, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - D.C. Houses: 122 D St. SE (includes photos), undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - D.C. Houses: 218-222 D St. SE, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - D.C. Houses: 703 D St. SE, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Houses: 806 D St. SE, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - D.C. Houses: 830 D St. SE, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - D.C. Houses: 127 E St. SE, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - D.C. Houses: 601 E St. SE, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - D.C. Houses: 517 East Capital St. SE, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - D.C. Houses: 621 East Capital St. SE, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - D.C. Houses: 647 East Capital St. SE (includes photos), undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - D.C. Houses: 600 Block G St. SE, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - D.C. Houses: 808 G St. SE, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - D.C. Houses: 1218 G St. SE, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - D.C. Houses: 312 Independence Ave. SE, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - D.C. Houses: 604 Independence Ave. SE, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - D.C. Houses: 642 Independence Ave. SE, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - D.C. Houses: 1009 Independence Ave. SE, undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - D.C. Houses: 1312 Independence Ave. SE, undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - D.C. Houses: 1217 Massachusetts Ave. SE, undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - D.C. Houses: 1312 Massachusetts Ave. SE (includes photos), undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - D.C. Houses: 448 New Jersey Ave. SE, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Houses: 816 North Carolina Ave. SE (includes photos), undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - D.C. Houses: 639 Pennsylvania Ave. SE, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - D.C. Houses: 901,902,904 Pennsylvania Ave. SE (includes photos), undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - D.C. Houses: 921 Pennsylvania Ave. SE Old Naval Hospital, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Houses: 1010 Pennsylvania Ave. SE, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - D.C. Houses: 1101 Pennsylvania Ave. SE, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - D.C. Houses: 915 Savannah St. SE, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - D.C. Houses: 1202 Walter St. SE, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Houses: 638 East Capital Alpine Bird, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - D.C. Houses: 807 East Capital St. Square 920 Lot 808, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - D.C. Houses: 1120 East Capital St., undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - D.C. Houses: 600 Independence Ave., undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - D.C. Houses: 1607 New Hampshire Ave., undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - D.C. Houses: 408 Seward Square SE The Wellerton Building, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - D.C. Houses: Square 454, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - D.C. Houses: Square 862, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - D.C. Houses: Square 939, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - D.C. Houses: Square 944, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - D.C. Houses: Square 1014, undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - D.C. Houses: Square 1019 Pennsylvania Ave., undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - D.C. Houses: Square 1064 Potomac Ave. SE, undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - D.C. Houses: Note cards--miscellaneous notes, undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - D.C. Houses: Note cards for Squares 609-780, undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - D.C. Houses: Note cards for Squares 780-904, undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - D.C. Houses: Note cards for Squares 902-926, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Houses: Note cards for Squares 905-1123, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - African-American topics: Deeds pre 1860, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - African-American topics: Emancipation, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - African-American topics: Emancipation in the District of Columbia, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - African-American topics: 1830 D.C. Free Blacks Heads of Households, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - African-American topics: Slavery in D.C. Clephane, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - African-American topics: Anti-slavery project, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - African-American topics: Pro-slavery petition, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - African-American topics: Thematic Study of Black Architects, Builders, and Developers in Washington, D.C. Phase I, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - American University Experiment Station and U.S. Navy Bomb Disposal School, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - American University Park Fesssenden, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Anacostia Park: Acts of Congress, 1924-1960; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Anacostia Park: An Analysis of Cultural Change in the Anacostia Valley thesis by Heather A. Wholey, 1997; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Anacostia Park: Archaeology, Circa 1938-1983; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Anacostia Park: Archaeology, Undated; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Anacostia Park: Archaeology of Barry's Farm, 1989; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Anacostia Park: Archaeology of recreation properties in Anacostia, 1984 September; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Anacostia Park: Army Engineers, 1912-1978; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Anacostia Park: Bridges, Anacostia, 1929-1987; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Anacostia Park: Channel depth, Circa 1890; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Anacostia Park: CFA annual report [Commission of Fine Arts], 1911-1940; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Anacostia Park: Draft [1/3], Circa 1999-2007; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Anacostia Park: Draft [2/3], Circa 1999-2007; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Anacostia Park: Draft [3/3], Circa 1999-2007; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Anacostia Park: Early Anacostia, Circa 1970-1984; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Anacostia Park: Field House, 1924; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Anacostia Park: Heine history [a history of national capital park by Cornelius W. Heine], 1953; MS23032 Series 6 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Anacostia Park: History, Undated; MS23032 Series 6 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Anacostia Park: Kenilworth Park, 1932-1996; MS23032 Series 6 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Anacostia Park: Langston Recreation Center and Golf Club, 1940-1954; MS23032 Series 6 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Anacostia Park: Maps, Circa 1860-1911; MS23032 Series 6 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Anacostia Park: Navy contract, Circa 1935; MS23032 Series 6 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Anacostia Park: Notes RG 328 [National Archives], 1924-1967; MS23032 Series 6 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Anacostia Park: Original land owners, Circa 1700; MS23032 Series 6 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Anacostia Park: Oxen Cove Park, 1997; MS23032 Series 6 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Anacostia Park: Outline and proposal for Anacostia Park history, 1999; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Anacostia Park: Parkside Playground correspondence, 1942-1957; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Anacostia Park: park development, 1937-1944; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Anacostia Park: A brief history of Section C, Anacostia National Park (Poplar Point), 2000 February; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Anacostia Park: Potomac River Basin, Potomac Park Levee operation and maintenance manual, 1963 June; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Anacostia Park: project files RG 66 [National Archives], 1915-1946; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Anacostia Park: Reclamation Anacostia Flats correspondence, 1947-1957; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Anacostia Park: research materials, 1909-1993; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Anacostia Park: Swimming pool, 1949, undated; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Anacostia Park: play areas, 1984-1995; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Anacostia Park: Washington Board of Trade, 1949; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Anacostia Park: Washington seawall, 1967; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Anacostia Park: yacht clubs and Seafarers attendees, 1926-1998; MS2032 Series 6 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Architecture: Barrier Legislation D.C., 1980 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Architecture: booklet "A Glossary of Historic Masonry Deterioration Problems and Preservation Treatments", 1997 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Architecture: Glossary of Architectural Surveys, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Architecture: Historic Landmark Application sample, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Architecture: Master D.C. Historic Preservation Office Survey database architecture reports, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Architecture: T. Franklin Schneider biography, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Architecture: Trusses Meigs, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Architecture: Vernacular Brick Bay Front etc., undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Architecture: Log and wood Vernacular Buildings, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Architecture: C.E. Webb biography, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Bicentennial promotional material for Overbeck and Robert Hughes (includes photos), 1974-1979 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Bicentennial, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Blacks in the Arts, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Blacks in the Arts: Wellington Adams, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Blacks in the Arts: Dr. Montague Cobb, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Blacks in the Arts: S. Coleridge, Andrew F. Hilyer, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Blacks in the Arts: Kim Deskins' Research Notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Blacks in the Arts: Data included in the directory, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Blacks in the Arts: Arthur Davis "A Washington Life", undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Blacks in the Arts: Todd Duncan taped interview June 21, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Blacks in the Arts: Lillian Evanti, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Blacks in the Arts: Angelina Weld Grimke Papers, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Blacks in the Arts: Sharon Harley file, undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Blacks in the Arts: Howard Theater (includes photos), undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Blacks in the Arts: Alain Locke, undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Blacks in the Arts: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Blacks in the Arts: Mu-So-Lit Club, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Blacks in the Arts: Newspaper Clippings from Washington Afro-American, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Blacks in the Arts: Notes, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Blacks in the Arts: Notebook (includes photos), undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Blacks in the Arts: Oral history project Shaw, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Blacks in the Arts: Proposal D.C. Blacks in the Arts, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Blacks in the Arts: Survey Material historic resources inventory buildings and structures, Undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Blacks in the Arts: Survey on-site houses District of Columbia historic resources inventory buildings and structures, Undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Blacks in the Arts: Survey of Shaw, Undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Blacks in the Arts: Survey of Shaw, Undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Blacks in the Arts: Theatre Guide of Washington, D.C., Undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Blacks in the Arts: "U Street" vertical file of Washingtoniana Division D.C.PL, Undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Blacks in the Arts: The Washington Bee, Undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Blacks in the Arts: Washington Conservatory, Undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Mordecai Booth 1814, Undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Robert Brent 1764-1819, Undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Bridge War, Undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Canal Street, Undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Capital City Market, Undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Capitol Hill: Article "Earliest Proprietors of Capitol Hill" by Margaret Brent Downing, 1917 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Capitol Hill: Article "Growing up Catholic" by Tom Kelly, Undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Capitol Hill: Article "Capitol Hill, 1870-1900 The People and Their Homes" by Susan Myers, Undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Capitol Hill: Church Capitol Hill Baptist Church, Undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Capitol Hill: Church Christ Church history, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Capitol Hill: Church St. James Church, undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Capitol Hill: Church Capitol Hill United Methodist Church, undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Capitol Hill: Church German immigration, undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Capitol Hill: Capitol Hill Group Ministry, undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Capitol Hill: Capitol Hill History, undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Capitol Hill: Market Row on Capitol Hill Newsletter, undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Capitol Hill: National Register nomination form Historic District, undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Capitol Hill: Pardoe collection Capitol Hill, an evolving community, undated (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Capitol Hill: Real Estate ads, undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Capitol Hill: Report: Capitol Hill Social History by Michael S. Franch, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Capitol Hill: Standards and Guidelines W.P.I. project for capitol hill restoration society, undated (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Capitol Hill: Study Capitol Hill Southeast a study of a residential area, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society: Article written by Overbeck in the CHRS newsletter Sept., 1978 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society: Directory, 1975-1978 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society: Historic Review Committee lecture/tour, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society: House and Garden Tour list of houses, 1958-1982 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society: House and Garden Tour program, 1971-1983 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society: House and Garden Tour program, 1977-1982 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society: House and Garden Tour programs (not inclusive), 1984-1999 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society: Speech "Lost Capitol Hill", 1979 (Box 18, Folder 8)